kevin teh designer's resumé.

Kevin Teh 27 Oct 1994 Malaysian

kevtlh@gmail.com +61 402 297 879 I believe that good design is all about reinforcing a positive experience for the intended audience, which can be achieved through a fine balance of fluidity and precision to make a subtle, but significant statement.

At least I think so.

education

Mar-Apr 2017

Academy Xi Sydney, Australia UX Design

2014-2016

Billy Blue College of Design Sydney, Australia Bachelor of Comm Design

2011-2013

Methodist College Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia A-Level (HSC Equivalent)

experiences

April 2017-May 2017

Marque Brand Consultants Sydney, Australia

Interning while designing
food packaging for
Woolworths.

May 2016-July 2016

Tiliqua Press Sydney, Australia

Designed style guide and magazine spreads for the second issue of Ligature Journal as the senior designer.

Aug 2015-Oct 2016

United Kingdom & Eire Malaysian Law Students' Union (KPUM) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Designed annual reports and prospectus and event booklets.

Sep 2012-July 2014

Methodist College Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Designed brochures and posters, and worked as a marketing intern.

Designed the 2012 yearbook in Vision Editorial Board, under the role of Head of Design Department.

July 2014-Feb 2015

United Kingdom Eire Council (UKEC) Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Designed promotional posters, event booklets and sponsorship booklet.

skills

Typography

This is my main strength which I use heavily in my design approach. I have a good eye for detail when it comes to layout designs.

Multilingualism

Native in Mandarin Chinese and Cantonese. Proficient in English and Malay. Elementarily proficient in Japanese.

Forward roll

A hidden talent of mine which I will be glad to perform under request on a carpeted floor. Please don't try this at home.